Hello friends I am Pranav Singh Abhinav here with
a new pan
and today's second question is going to be
presented on your screen very soon so
this is the second question till today he is presented on his own spin the
question is that you are Reddy
warriors wheeler on road notification petrol
mukti mil drowned option a slow down and
requested also portal click continue
driving in soil service to your right WiFi
portal home owners royal indian express
headlight wander application so what will you give
dec21 option is now into the river in
India where the question is that while driving on the road
you notice that there is a
road protector then you will do this
when you are driving on the side and reversing
that is the first answer of its kind will all be done
innocent person will cross the portal now
and will cross this portal carefully that is that will continue to deal with to continue
going on in this piece and if you want then I can do this
and that is when you go
and add to do the other  For this they do
the problem tube skin and I request you
friends and we are
getting the use of it now everything is fine, we are
tagging people with our hands on social media,
then I want to thank you very much
Hansa Rolls, our 15 winners are getting prizes
and now it will reach them on their own,
we also
thank the people of India for their willingness to send that prize,
this program has been started by
ICICI Lombard, Singh's
slogan is 2 minutes behind Protect Your Family
and you can see these questions on their social media channels too,
but
friends, now to answer, you will have to come to the
link of our India Against Congress,
you will have to
register your correct answer there, there you will have to
register your name and address, only then your name will be registered in the glass of winners which is made, in which those who give correct answers get prizes,
otherwise you will only apply sorting on us if you have total
and you will not register
in the website and friends, now if the answer is
anywhere, please give it
Your name will not be included in the winners list and you
may be deprived of getting a name, so friends
please play, like and
share it and whatever problem you have,
friends I hope that
our channel will get it and you will
also do it for you and your family and they will
help you, so I hope
friends and our guests please
subscribe and that too
is Rudrapur in India, in this way they are the
people who have got the race together, these
people got votes, they got the
proposal to work in the field of road safety and to ensure its
compliance, they have appealed that if you
walk on this road and any
person in bad condition, friends, help him, now
you cannot fulfill it, no one can trouble you,
so you have to select the
subscription which you feel can be done
after helping, then
you will not have any incentive under this school, if
you want your name, address,
tiger, only then you will be called for testimony
and friends, if this medicine is
very important for you, then it will be
taken from you as per your convenience and you will not be forced to pay it.  You will get it in
friends, if you help anyone then
you will be stopped in this way also, so
friends now
it is named Good Morning on your stomach and on
social media, if you eat then you
can also add it while roaming, you will see it in the name of Good Time Extreme,
if you enter prosperity then
you will get balance and you
can read about it on a large scale, there are
three different police in it, two according to them,
it has been decided for the growth of doctors
and two for the general public, so that means we
want to help people like me and you who call them liquids,
full protection has been kept on them also,
many guides have been seen for them
and they are also starting to promote their strong vegetables,
recently the Jharkhand government has just
issued a notification that by making
its partner, you get a
cash reward along with the quality help system,
if you are a resident of Thoda and are
listening to me, then you should
fully participate in this effort of your government,
help the people, friends  We
took help from a lot of people and we can help a lot of people and in that
friends and you too can still be
in the answer that how much we are
looking at the injured in an accident
friends now we have no problem with that then
we should help them friends if you
want to subscribe so friends when there is a
problem in life then most of the time the answer to that problem is life, your answer is a
big help then anything can happen in this world
friends you have got life you have been
given this life by god you have come into human life you have done such a big
virtue due to which
you have been born in human form so to make
it meaningful
we cannot give a bigger proof and fire than this friends
we can help an accident victim
immediately contact any method if
you are not able to take him to hospital if you do not have the means then at
least turn on the
ambulance call the police will take him
there you stay with him till he gets some help
friends give us this much we can buy
friends this little
effort of yours can save so many lives
friends and
our honorable Prime Minister also spoke to
us last Sunday  I
request you to come forward and
help people,
friends, we can help in that too
and we can participate in the development of our country,
friends,
because the economic loss that occurs due to these
deaths, whether it is due to any reason,
accident happened due to our negligence,
after the accident we stayed away,
they did not help the person, he was
not taken to the hospital properly, he was
not taken to the hospital on time and if
any person dies due to that, the
economic loss that India suffers due to that is
huge, friends, that three to
four percent is due to our policies and you know that the
entire education budget of India, the
entire education budget of India is as much as
Mother Teresa, every year we have to bear the loss due to the deaths that occur in road accidents, the
entire government has to bear it
and we have to motivate that subject,
now Suji, if we fully
support and see comment, first of all we
should drive safely, accidents are bound to happen
and then if accidents have occurred due to any reason
and at least
that person should be helped  Help her, take her to the hospital immediately so that she does
not die, we will manage her and
we have our part in it, she should keep her
safe, oh two slogans, we are Narayan in the container,
if we save that girl
and we are doing Narayan and time in it,
friends, you become Narayan,
all the gods will descend on you, if you reach there
and
help her at that time, then whatever you need, then at that
time the person will
definitely come to help you, that if you helped
someone in need till that day, then you helped him, so
friends, it is the same thing in life
that you will make money, the same thing happens with you too, so
if you help someone
and now there is legal protection, then that is
not the beginning of fear, rather
you will get praise from the Aghor report,
people will praise you and
that too, the biggest thing you get in Mandsaur, the
happy feeling that you get from the family members of the robber whom you help right now, there is no
comparison to that, there is no
money, no
award, nothing for you, friend, just two
You feel satisfaction when you
help someone, so you were a devotee, so
friends, I would just request you on this voice that
you will move forward, become a good
man, friends, help people
when you are in such a place, now you can also think
that why is it till Nakul, why has God brought you
there at that time,
so this can also be a
message from the manifest that you are here
in that situation, the injured person is there, that is why the
manifest expects from you
that you will play your part and you can help in
every possible way to save that person's life, so the
help of calling an ambulance also becomes
very big friends because
even after that, if all the talks and things are going on, the hospital can
reach immediately on time and his
treatment can also be done, so friends, calling is
also a very big thing and at the
time of calling, friends, I would like to tell you one more thing
that you call the ambulance
service, or any such emergency service, or the
police, how to handle any incident, so
you can understand a little about the incidents  If
they tell the location clearly then it is
easy to get it from there,
they can reach there very quickly, by their
immediate information of the incident, if you see that
in the proposed accident, one thousand people have been
injured, then you will tell them this on the phone, there are
more people and if you
remember a pregnant woman in it, if you
also tell them about that in advance that there is
a pregnant woman among the injured and two
ambulances have to be arranged, they will
come a little and they can help in a better way, so
such things also, whatever
you feel like in that incident, then you should
make it now, if the location of the incident is mentioned,
tell me some landmark of Ujjain, it is
easy to find it, because due to
not reaching different places with the same name, it is not
complete, it gets
spoiled, so
you are turning on that too, friends, so at that
time tell a little, which is the most important thing that you have,
definitely tell how many people have been injured, if there is
any per month or there are any, we will inform about it in
advance and if anyone you
and you here smart line number  If you know someone, you
can give them their number
so that they can contact them later for the
right way to get pregnant powder. These were
very small things but they become very big
worries. Then emergency situation
means that at that time a lot of time is
wasted and this is the time that has to be told
and we cannot do anything because the
treatment of the patient will only create problems. You do
n't have to remember it but you have to
tell him that it is his lifelong time and
he can tell me that in a single bed it is
very precious for every person
and what kind of death we have and we
can help so much in such a short time. We need to learn this and
we need to be aware of this.
Friends, today I think when you
hear this, you will realize a little bit about
how should I help so that we can
help more in less time without seeing that person and
we can also make Bhagiratha efforts in removing the pain. So
friends, I put this
question before you once again.
Your riding fronts are available at
Nehru Road Notification Toll Plaza.  Nay
Negotiate Nipple Wash Will Continue
Driving And Were To Your Right Brothers
Pole Damaged And City Michael D E F
Entry Youth More To Do Friends Whenever You Go Out Stay
Safe Take Full Care
And Take Care Of Yourself And If You
Need Any Personal Help Then
Please Subscribe